spectrumng.net 2016-04-02

# Club Management Software, Membership Management Software, Parks and Recreation, Health Club, Fitness Management Software - CSI Software

## CSI Software Privacy Statement

This document was last updated August 1, 2003.

CSI Software is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement only applies to CSI Software.com; it does not apply to other online or offline CSI Software sites, products or services. Please read the complete CSI Software privacy statement.

#### Collection of your Personal Information

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are registering before entering a contest, ordering e-mail newsletters, joining a limited-access premium site, signing up for an event or training, or when purchasing and/or registering CSI Software product information. Personal information collected by CSI Software often is limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.

For example: If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase in the Request Form of the Web site, we will request personal information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number.

When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register your purchase electronically. We keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site.

CSI Software also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser type, operating system, domain name, access times and referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of CSI Software.com. 

CSI Software also collects information about which pages our customers visit within CSI Software.com. This site visitation data is identified only by a unique ID number, and it is never linked with personal information unless a user consents as described below.

CSI Software uses .NET Passport as its registration and authentication service. When you sign in to this site using .NET Passport, you will be asked to provide your e-mail address and a password to sign you in. This same Passport sign-in allows you to access many other Passport participating sites and services. To learn more about the Passport service, the information stored in the Passport profile, and how Passport uses and protects your personal information, please read the .NET Passport privacy statement.

#### Use of your Personal Information

We use your personal information for the following purposes:

  * • To ensure our site is relevant to your needs.
  * • To deliver services, such as newsletters, events, training or software, that you request or purchase.
  * • To help us create and publish content most relevant to you.
  * • To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new services from CSI Software, if you so request.
  * • To allow you access to limited-entry areas of our site as appropriate.

We will merge site-visitation data with anonymous demographic information for research purposes, and we may use this information in aggregate to provide more relevant content. In some limited-entry sections of CSI Software.com, with your approval, we will combine site-visitation data with your personal information in order to provide you with personalized content. If you decline permission, we will not provide you the personalized service and won't merge your personal information with site-visitation data.

We occasionally hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging, mailing and delivering purchases, answering customer questions about products or services, sending postal mail and processing event registration. We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose. 

CSI Software may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on CSI Software or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of CSI Software and its family of Web sites, or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of CSI Software employees, users of CSI Software products or services, or members of the public.

Your information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which CSI Software or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities, and by using this site, you consent to any such transfer of information outside of your country. CSI Software abides by the safe harbor framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of data from the European Union.

#### Control of your Personal Information

When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, CSI Software will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.

Registering also allows you to tell us how or whether you want CSI Software to communicate with you. After registering, go to the Profile Center and establish your preferences in the Contact Options sections. There, you can decide what information you want to receive and how you want to receive it. Or you can tell us not to contact you by removing check marks from the contact option boxes. If you buy software through CSI Software.com, and do not want to receive such information, do not check the box on the Checkout page (or on other pages where personal information is collected) which says: Yes, I would like to receive other offers through.CSI Software..

CSI Software may send out periodic e-mails informing you of technical service or security issues related to a product or service you requested, or confirming you requested a product or service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have chosen.Access to your Personal Information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current.

#### Security of your Personal Information

CSI Software is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide in computer servers with limited access that are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.Protection of Children's Personal Information

CSI Software is a general audience site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

#### Use of Cookies

When someone visits the site, a cookie is placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above.

We also use cookies to collect information on which newsletter links are clicked by customers. This information is used to ensure we are sending information customers want to read. It is collected in aggregate form and never linked with your personal information.

Web beacons, also known as clear gif technology, or action tags, may be used to assist in delivering the cookie on our site. This technology tells us how many visitors clicked on key elements (such as links or graphics) on a CSI Software Web page. We do not use this technology to access your personally identifiable information on CSI Software.com; it is a tool we use to compile aggregated statistics about CSI Software Web site usage. We may share aggregated site statistics with partner companies but do not allow other companies to place clear gifs on our sites.

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the CSI Software Web site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the site.

#### Enforcement of this Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact CSI Software by [support@csisoftwareusa.com](mailto:support@csisoftwareusa.com).

#### Changes to this Statement

CSI Software will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "last updated" date at the top of the privacy statement. For material changes to this statement, CSI Software will notify you by placing prominent notice on the Web site.Contact Information.

CSI Software welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement, please contact us by [support@csisoftwareusa.com](mailto:support@csisoftwareusa.com), or postal mail.

CSI Software Privacy  
5252 Westchester, Suite 250  
Houston, TX 77005
